Theertha Sreebhesh



About Me

MSc Computing student with two years of experience in front-end web development. Strong creative and design talents, as well as a strong work ethic. A good team member is willing to accept mistakes and replace them effectively.



Contact



+447833850791



theerthasreebhesh@gmail. com



18, Farm View, Hill Of Beath, Cowdenbeath, Fife, Scotland



Expertise

FRONT END

- HTML
- CSS
- Java Scipt

PROGRAMMING LANGUAGES

- C
- OOPs- Java

Language

- English
- Hindi



Education

(2022-present)

NAPIER UNIVERSITY, UK

MSc Computing

(2011-2014)

SENGUNTHAR ENGGINEERING **COLLEGE, INDIA**

Master of Computer Application

(2009-2011)

PROVIDENCE WOMENCE **COLLEGE, INDIA**

Bachelor of Computer Science



Experience

(2018-2022

IT TEACHER

Calorx Public School, India

(2017 - 2019)

JUNIOR WEB DEVELOPER

Akash Foundations, India